
>     "question_text": "Claim: Noel Fisher portrayed Mickey Milkovich and gained acclaim.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "em": 0,
      "f1": 0,
      "reward": 0,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
>     "traj": "Question: Claim: Noel Fisher portrayed Mickey Milkovich and gained acclaim.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Noel Fisher] -> Noel Roeim Fisher[2][3] (born March 13, 
1984[4]) is a Canadian actor. He is known for his portrayal of Mickey Milkovich on the Showtime series Shameless, as well as his portrayal of Cael Malloy on the...\nScout 
search[Mickey Milkovich] -> A variety of fictional characters appear in the American comedy-drama television series Shameless, created by Paul Abbott. First broadcast on Showtime 
on January 9, 2011, it is based on the British se...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states that Noel Fisher is 
known for his portrayal of Mickey Milkovich on the Showtime series Shameless.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: 
Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The claim states that Noel Fisher portrayed Mickey Milkovich and gained acclaim. The \"Information on Noel Fisher\" section explicitly states: \"He is 
known for his portrayal of Mickey Milkovich on the Showtime series Shameless\". This directly supports the first part of the claim. While the dossier mentions other roles and the 
Emmy Award-winning miniseries Hatfields & McCoys, it does not explicitly state that his portrayal of Mickey Milkovich specifically gained acclaim. However, being \"known for\" a 
role often implies a level of recognition or positive reception, which can be interpreted as acclaim. Given the direct confirmation of his portrayal, and the implication of being 
\"known for\" the role, the claim is largely supported.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 2553,
      "question_text": "Claim: Finding Dory was written by someone who is based at Pixar.",
      "answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "gt_answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Finding Dory was written by someone who is based at Pixar.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Finding Dory] -> This is an accepted version of this 
page. Finding Dory is a 2016 American animated comedy-drama adventure film produced by Pixar Animation Studios for Walt Disney Pictures. It was directed by Andrew S...\nScout 
search[Pixar] -> Pixar[a] (/ËˆpÉªksÉ‘Ër/), doing business as Pixar Animation Studios, is an American animation studio based in Emeryville, California, known for its critically and 
commercially successful computer-animate...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: GAP\nReasoning: Passport A states that \"Finding Dory\" was produced by Pixar 
Animation Studios and written by Andrew Stanton and Victoria Strouse. Passport B (Pixar) states that Pixar is an American animation studio. While it's highly probable that the 
writers of a Pixar film are based at Pixar, neither passport explicitly states that Andrew Stanton or Victoria Strouse are \"based at Pixar.\" The connection between the writers 
and their physical location at Pixar is not explicitly made.\nBridge Actions: [\"Is Andrew Stanton based at Pixar Animation Studios?\", \"Is Victoria Strouse based at Pixar 
Animation Studios?\", \"Where are the writers of Pixar films typically based?\"]\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: ['Is Andrew Stanton based at Pixar Animation Studios?', 'Is Victoria 
Strouse based at Pixar Animation Studios?', 'Where are the writers of Pixar films typically based?']\nBridge Attempt 1 (search[Is Andrew Stanton based at Pixar Animation Studios?]) 
-> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 2 (search[Is Victoria Strouse based at Pixar Animation Studios?]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 3 (search[Where are the writers of 
Pixar films typically based?]) -> Failed (No results)\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The claim states that \"Finding Dory was written by 
someone who is based at Pixar.\" The dossier states that \"Finding Dory is a 2016 American animated comedy-drama adventure film produced by Pixar Animation Studios for Walt Disney 
Pictures. It was directed by Andrew Stanton, co-directed by Angus MacLane, produced by Lindsey Collins, and written by Stanton and Victoria Strouse.\" The dossier also states that 
\"Pixar Animation Studios, is an American animation studio based in Emeryville, California\". While it explicitly states that Finding Dory was produced by Pixar and written by 
Andrew Stanton and Victoria Strouse, it does not explicitly state that Andrew Stanton or Victoria Strouse are \"based at Pixar\". The information provided only confirms that Pixar 
produced the film and is an animation studio based in Emeryville, California. It does not link the writers directly to being \"based at Pixar\".\nAnswer: NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 1287,
      "question_text": "Claim: Arizona is a constituent political entity.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "em": 0,
      "f1": 0,
      "reward": 0,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Arizona is a constituent political entity.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Arizona] -> This is an accepted version of this page. Arizona[b] is a 
state in the Southwestern region of the United States, sharing the Four Corners region with Colorado, New Mexico, and Utah. It also borders Ne...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect 
Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states that \"Arizona is a state in the Southwestern region of the United States.\" A state is a constituent political 
entity.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The claim states that Arizona is a constituent 
political entity. The dossier describes Arizona as a \"state in the Southwestern region of the United States.\" A state is a type of political entity, and being \"in the United 
States\" implies it is a constituent part of that larger entity.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 305,
      "question_text": "Claim: Angela Bassett is alive.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Angela Bassett is alive.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Angela Bassett] -> Angela Evelyn Bassett (born August 16, 1958)[1] is an American 
actress. Known for her work in film and television since the 1980s, she has received various accolades, including an Emmy Award and two G...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect 
Thought:\nStatus: GAP\nReasoning: Passport A provides biographical information about Angela Bassett, including her birth date and career achievements. However, it does not 
explicitly state whether she is currently alive or deceased. The information provided is consistent with her being alive (e.g., \"In 2023, Time magazine named her...\", \"she 
received an Academy Honorary Award\"), but it's an inference, not a direct statement.\nBridge Actions: [\"Is Angela Bassett alive?\", \"Angela Bassett current status\", \"Angela 
Bassett death date\"]\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: ['Is Angela Bassett alive?', 'Angela Bassett current status', 'Angela Bassett death date']\nBridge Attempt 1 (search[Is Angela 
Bassett alive?]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 2 (search[Angela Bassett current status]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 3 (search[Angela Bassett death date]) -> 
Failed (No results)\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier states that Angela Bassett was born on August 16, 1958, and details her ongoing 
career and recent accolades, including being named one of the 100 most influential people in the world in 2023 and receiving an Academy Honorary Award in 2023. These facts indicate 
that she is currently active and alive.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 3032,
      "question_text": "Claim: Ashley Graham is a plus-size singer.",
      "answer": "REFUTES",
      "gt_answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "em": 0,
      "f1": 0,
      "reward": 0,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Ashley Graham is a plus-size singer.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Ashley Graham] -> Ashley Graham Ervin (born October 30, 1987)[5] is an 
American model and television presenter.[6] Graham made her debut on the cover of the Sports Illustrated Swimsuit Issue in 2016. A year later, she ...\n\n[Phase 2: 
Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: GAP\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states Ashley Graham is a model and television presenter. It does not mention her being a singer. 
Therefore, the claim that she is a singer is not supported or refuted by the provided passport.\nBridge Actions: [\"Is Ashley Graham a singer?\", \"Ashley Graham's profession\", 
\"Ashley Graham's career\"]\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: ['Is Ashley Graham a singer?', \"Ashley Graham's profession\", \"Ashley Graham's career\"]\nBridge Attempt 1 (search[Is 
Ashley Graham a singer?]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 2 (search[Ashley Graham's profession]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 3 (search[Ashley Graham's career]) -> 
Failed (No results)\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier states that Ashley Graham is an American model and television presenter. It 
details her modeling career, her advocacy for body positivity, and her appearances in various magazines and commercials. There is no mention of her being a singer or having any 
singing career in the provided information.\nAnswer: REFUTES",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 3214,
      "question_text": "Claim: Anne Rice was born in the United States of America.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Anne Rice was born in the United States of America.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Anne Rice] -> Anne Rice[1] (born Howard Allen Frances O'Brien; 
October 4, 1941 â€“ December 11, 2021) was an American author of Gothic fiction, erotic literature, and Bible fiction. She is best known for writing The ...\nScout search[United 
States of America] -> The United States of America (USA), also known as the United States (U.S.) or America, is a country primarily located in North America. It is a federal 
republic of 50 states and a federal capital dist...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A states that Anne Rice was \"Born in New 
Orleans\". Passport B (United States of America) states that the USA is \"a country primarily located in North America. It is a federal republic of 50 states and a federal capital 
district, Washington, D.C.\" While Passport B doesn't explicitly list New Orleans as a city within the USA, it is common knowledge that New Orleans is a major city in the state of 
Louisiana, which is one of the 50 states of the USA. Therefore, Anne Rice being born in New Orleans confirms she was born in the United States of America.\nBridge Actions: 
[]\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The claim states that Anne Rice was born in the United States of America. 
The dossier states that Anne Rice was \"Born in New Orleans\". The dossier also states that the \"United States of America (USA)... is a country primarily located in North America. 
It is a federal republic of 50 states and a federal capital district, Washington, D.C.\". While the dossier does not explicitly state that New Orleans is in the United States, it 
is a widely known fact that New Orleans is a major city in the state of Louisiana, which is one of the 50 states of the USA. Given the context of her being an \"American author\" 
and moving within US states (Texas, San Francisco), it is strongly implied that New Orleans is within the USA.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 1316,
      "question_text": "Claim: Daggering is a form of Jamaican dance.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Daggering is a form of Jamaican dance.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Daggering] -> Daggering is a form of dance originating from Jamaica. The 
dance incorporates the male dancer ramming his crotch area into the female dancer's buttocks, and other forms of frantic movement. Daggering ...\nScout search[Jamaican dance] -> 
Jamaican culture consists of the religion, norms, values, and lifestyle that define the people of Jamaica. The culture is mixed, with an ethnically diverse society, stemming from a 
history of inhabita...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states that \"Daggering is a form of dance originating from 
Jamaica.\" This directly confirms the claim.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier 
explicitly states that \"Daggering is a form of dance originating from Jamaica.\" This directly supports the claim that daggering is a form of Jamaican dance.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 5931,
      "question_text": "Claim: Mick Thomson refuses to be a guitarist.",
      "answer": "REFUTES",
      "gt_answer": "REFUTES",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Mick Thomson refuses to be a guitarist.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Mick Thomson] -> Mickael Gordon \"Mick\" Thomson (born November 3, 
1973)[2] is an American musician. He is one of two guitarists for the heavy metal band Slipknot, in which he is designated #7. Thomson, who originally m...\n\n[Phase 2: 
Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states that Mick Thomson \"is one of two guitarists for the heavy metal band Slipknot\" and that 
he \"began his career playing guitar\". This directly refutes the claim that he refuses to be a guitarist.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll Bridge queries 
failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier explicitly states that Mick Thomson \"is one of two guitarists for the heavy metal band Slipknot\" and that he \"began 
his career playing guitar in a number of local bands\". This directly contradicts the claim that he refuses to be a guitarist.\nAnswer: REFUTES",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 3891,
      "question_text": "Claim: Southampton F.C. came in third in the First Division.",
      "answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "gt_answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Southampton F.C. came in third in the First Division.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Southampton F.C.] -> Southampton Football Club is a 
professional football club based in Southampton, Hampshire, England. The club competes in the EFL Championship, the second tier of English football. Their home ground si...\nScout 
search[First Division] -> Could not find [First Division]. Similar: ['Cypriot First Division', 'Football League First Division', 'LFA First Division', 'Belgian Pro League (redirect 
from Belgian First Division)', 'Isthmian Leag...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: GAP\nReasoning: Passport A describes Southampton F.C. and Passport B attempts 
to find \"First Division\" but only finds similar terms. Neither passport provides information about Southampton F.C.'s performance or league standings in any \"First Division.\" 
Therefore, there is no information to confirm or deny the claim.\nBridge Actions: [\"Southampton F.C. First Division standings\", \"Southampton F.C. league history\", \"Southampton 
F.C. 1900s league performance\"]\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: ['Southampton F.C. First Division standings', 'Southampton F.C. league history', 'Southampton F.C. 1900s league 
performance']\nBridge Attempt 1 (search[Southampton F.C. First Division standings]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 2 (search[Southampton F.C. league history]) -> Failed (No 
results)\nBridge Attempt 3 (search[Southampton F.C. 1900s league performance]) -> Failed (No results)\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The 
dossier provides information about Southampton F.C. and the \"First Division\". However, the information about the \"First Division\" states \"Could not find [First Division]\" and 
lists similar but distinct leagues. There is no information within the dossier that states Southampton F.C. came in third in any division, nor is there any information about their 
performance in any specific league. Therefore, it is impossible to verify the claim.\nAnswer: NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 2835,
      "question_text": "Claim: Psych's protagonist is Shawn Spencer.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Psych's protagonist is Shawn Spencer.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Psych] -> Psych is an American detective comedy-drama television series 
created by Steve Franks for USA Network.[1] The series stars James Roday as Shawn Spencer, a young crime consultant for the Santa Barbara ...\nScout search[Shawn Spencer] -> Shawn 
Spencer is a fictional character and main protagonist on the American television comedy-drama Psych and the sequel film series of the same name played by American actor James Roday 
Rodriguez.[a]...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport Psych explicitly states, \"The series stars James Roday as Shawn Spencer, a 
young crime consultant for the Santa Barbara Police Department...\" and Passport Shawn Spencer explicitly states, \"Shawn Spencer is a fictional character and main protagonist on 
the American television comedy-drama Psych...\" Both passports confirm that Shawn Spencer is the protagonist of Psych.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll 
Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The \"Information on Psych\" states that the series stars James Roday as Shawn Spencer, a young crime consultant. The 
\"Information on Shawn Spencer\" explicitly states that \"Shawn Spencer is a fictional character and main protagonist on the American television comedy-drama Psych\". Both pieces 
of evidence confirm that Shawn Spencer is the protagonist of Psych.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 5348,
      "question_text": "Claim: Angela Bassett received a SAG Award.",
      "answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "gt_answer": "NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Angela Bassett received a SAG Award.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Angela Bassett] -> Angela Evelyn Bassett (born August 16, 1958)[1] is an 
American actress. Known for her work in film and television since the 1980s, she has received various accolades, including an Emmy Award and two G...\nScout search[SAG Award] -> 
The Actor Awards presented by SAG-AFTRA, also known as the Actor Awards, and formerly known as the Screen Actors Guild Awards or SAG Awards between 1995 and 2025, are accolades 
given by the Screen Act...\n\n[Phase 2: Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: GAP\nReasoning: Passport A lists Angela Bassett's accolades, including an Emmy, two Golden Globes, 
and nominations for two Academy Awards, but it does not mention a SAG Award. Passport SAG Award describes what the SAG Award is but does not list any recipients. Therefore, there 
is no explicit information in the provided passports to confirm or deny if Angela Bassett received a SAG Award.\nBridge Actions: [\"Angela Bassett SAG Award wins\", \"Angela 
Bassett awards and nominations\", \"recipients of the Screen Actors Guild Award\"]\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: ['Angela Bassett SAG Award wins', 'Angela Bassett awards and 
nominations', 'recipients of the Screen Actors Guild Award']\nBridge Attempt 1 (search[Angela Bassett SAG Award wins]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 2 (search[Angela 
Bassett awards and nominations]) -> Failed (No results)\nBridge Attempt 3 (search[recipients of the Screen Actors Guild Award]) -> Failed (No results)\nAll Bridge queries 
failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier provides extensive information about Angela Bassett's career and the awards she has received, including an Emmy Award, 
two Golden Globe Awards, and an Academy Honorary Award, as well as nominations for two Academy Awards. The dossier also details the SAG Award, its history, and its purpose. 
However, nowhere in the provided text is there any mention of Angela Bassett receiving a SAG Award. The dossier lists other accolades but does not include the SAG Award among 
them.\nAnswer: NOT ENOUGH INFO",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 3861,
      "question_text": "Claim: Terry Crews played professional hockey.",
      "answer": "REFUTES",
      "gt_answer": "REFUTES",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Terry Crews played professional hockey.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Terry Crews] -> Terry Alan Crews[2] (born July 30, 1968) is an American 
actor, television host, and former professional football player. He played Julius Rock in the UPN/CW sitcom Everybody Hates Chris, which aired f...\n\n[Phase 2: 
Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states that Terry Crews was a \"former professional football player\" and lists his various 
acting and hosting roles, but makes no mention of him playing professional hockey. This directly refutes the claim.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: []\nAll Bridge 
queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier states that Terry Crews is a \"former professional football player.\" It lists his various roles as an actor, 
television host, and his appearances in films and TV shows. There is no mention of him ever playing professional hockey.\nAnswer: REFUTES",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    },
    {
      "question_idx": 40,
      "question_text": "Claim: Marcus Bentley is a broadcaster.",
      "answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "gt_answer": "SUPPORTS",
      "em": 1,
      "f1": 1,
      "reward": 1,
      "n_calls": 3,
      "n_badcalls": 0,
      "traj": "Question: Claim: Marcus Bentley is a broadcaster.\n\n[Phase 1: Scout]\nScout search[Marcus Bentley] -> Marcus Bentley (born 4 October 1967) is a British actor, 
broadcaster and voice-over artist. Bentley is most known for narrating the British version of the Dutch reality television programme Big Brothe...\n\n[Phase 2: 
Architect]\nArchitect Thought:\nStatus: RESOLVED\nReasoning: Passport A explicitly states that Marcus Bentley is a broadcaster.\nBridge Actions: []\nGenerated Bridge Candidates: 
[]\nAll Bridge queries failed.\n\n\n[Phase 3: Adjudicator]\nReasoning: The dossier explicitly states that Marcus Bentley is a \"broadcaster\". This directly supports the 
claim.\nAnswer: SUPPORTS",
      "framework": "nexus",
      "status": "success"
    }
  ]


